<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Researches on CNI Engineering Lab</title><link>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/</link><description>Recent content in Researches on CNI Engineering Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 23:19:06 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Neural Decoding with Kernel-based Metric Learning</title><link>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/neural_decoding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 23:19:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/neural_decoding/</guid><description>Overview When studying the nervous system, the choice of metric for the neural responses is a pivotal assumption. A well-suited distance metric enables neuroscientists to gauge the similarity of neural responses to various stimuli and assess the variability of responses to a repeated stimulus. In particular, neural spike train metrics have been used to quantify the information content carried by the timing of action potentials. While a number of metrics for individual neurons exist, a method to optimally combine single-neuron metrics into multi-neuron, or population-based, metrics is lacking.</description></item><item><title>Learning Recurrent Waveforms within EEGs</title><link>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/eegs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 22:42:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/eegs/</guid><description>Overview When experts analyze EEGs they look for landmarks in the traces corresponding to established patterns such as oscillatory and phasic events of particular frequency or morphology. Long records motivate automated analysis techniques. Automation techniques often require design choices such as wavelet family or number of bandpass filters. To overcome this, we explore a modeling approach that automatically learns recurrent temporal waveforms within EEG traces. The estimation is based on a multiple-input, single-output linear model with sparsely excited inputs.</description></item><item><title>Quantifying the informativeness of similarity measurements</title><link>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/informativeness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 21:25:29 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/informativeness/</guid><description>Overview Choosing the particulars of a data representation is crucial for the successful application of machine learning techniques. In the unsupervised case, there is a lack of measures that can be used to compare different parameter choices that affect the representation. In this paper, we describe an unsupervised measure for quantifying the &amp;lsquo;informativeness&amp;rsquo; of correlation matrices formed from the pairwise similarities or relationships among data instances.
The measure quantifies the heterogeneity of the correlations and is defined as the distance between a correlation matrix and the nearest correlation matrix with constant off-diagonal entries.</description></item><item><title>External Link</title><link>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:59:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://annapoliswu.github.io/CNI_Lab/research/test/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>