<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Singles on CNIEL - University of Delaware</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Singles on CNIEL - University of Delaware</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 12:00:01 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 12:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 02:38:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/education/</guid>
      <description>Fall semesters: second-year graduate-level course in machine learning. Spring 2023: second-year graduate course with industry proposed team projects focused on Computing and Data Science for Soft Materials Innovation (co-teaching with lead instructor Prof. Arthi Jayaraman) Spring 2023: In development: a 300-level undergraduate course in geospatial data science (co-teaching with Prof. Jing Gao and Prof. Gregory Dobler Spring 2022–: NRT-MIDAS NSF funded research traineeship, serving as Core Faculty and secondary advisor for trainees Spring 2020, 2021, 2022: 300-level undergraduate course in signal processing and linear system analysis Summer 2021: Independent study on adaptive filters Spring 2021: Graduate Data Science Community Hour during Spring 2020 Graduate Course Large-Scale Machine Learning ELEG/FSAN 817 Course Description: Introduction to the analysis and processing of massive high-dimensional data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K–12 Outreach and Undergraduate Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:49:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/outreach/</guid>
      <description>In 2019, we joined UD&amp;rsquo;s Women in Engineering outreach program at a local New Castle Middle School, Serviam Girls Academy, whose mission is to take girls from low-income houses and give them the education they need to succeed in high school and beyond. Working with Trevor Foresta, ECE undergraduate student and Julia Schneider, a post-doctoral researcher from the Department of Linguistics and Cognitive Sciences, we developed a module showing ECE’s critical role in neuroimaging technology and analysis for their enrichment program during their enrichment hour (4-5 pm on Wednesday).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admissions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/admissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:49:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/~ajbrock/singles/admissions/</guid>
      <description>Application Deadlines  University of Delaware&amp;rsquo;s Ph.D. program in Electrical and Computer Engineering (apply early; February 1 is the deadline to be considered for departmental funding.) University of Delaware&amp;rsquo;s Undergraduate Summer Scholars (Please contact me ASAP as deadlines are usually Feb. or Mar.) University of Delaware&amp;rsquo;s Latin and South America Summer Program for Visiting Researchers (Deadline TBD for 2023)  It is unlikely that I can respond to email requests regarding positions in my group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
